nyfuturestars.com 2008-12-17

# View topic - NYFS Privacy Policy ny mets message boards forums mets minor league baseball discussion group

[NYFS](http://www.nyfuturestars.com/) Privacy Policy:

This [NYFS](http://www.nyfuturestars.com/) Privacy Policy describes the privacy practices that apply to [NYFS](http://www.nyfuturestars.com/)'s products, services and websites collectively, [NYFS](http://www.nyfuturestars.com/)'s "services". 

[NYFS](http://www.nyfuturestars.com/) collects personal information when you register for an [NYFS](http://www.nyfuturestars.com/) service or otherwise voluntarily provide such information to provide a better user experience, including customizing content for you. 

[NYFS](http://www.nyfuturestars.com/) NEVER sells your personal information to any third party. [NYFS](http://www.nyfuturestars.com/) NEVER sends unsolicited email advertisements (i.e., Spam) to you. We collect your personal information to provide you with a customized user experience. 

[NYFS](http://www.nyfuturestars.com/) uses cookies and other technologies to enhance and customize your user experience and to learn about how you use [NYFS](http://www.nyfuturestars.com/) services in order to improve the quality of our web sites and content. 

[NYFS](http://www.nyfuturestars.com/)'s servers automatically record information when you visit our website or use some of our products, including the URL, IP address, browser type and language, and the date and time of your request. 

We may use personal information to provide the services you've requested, including services that display customized content. 

We may also share information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services. 

You may decline to provide personal information to us and/or refuse cookies in your browser, although some of our features or services may not function properly as a result.  
_________________  
PLEASE Take a moment today to install the NYFS/Alexa Toolbar. No advertising or spyware. It anonymously tracks your web usage of NYFS so we can demonstrate our audience to sponsors thru a third party and keep paying the bills. The Alexa bar supports Firefox browsers so everyone can help. It takes 30 seconds, and is a HUGE help to NYFS.
